{
  "DeckName": "Hiragana Words vol2",
  "LanguageCode": "ja-JP",
  "DeckEnabled": true,
  "Cards": [
    {
      "Question": "ほん",
      "Narration": "hon",
      "Answer": "book"
    },
    {
      "Question": "じしょ",
      "Narration": "jisho",
      "Answer": "dictionary"
    },
    {
      "Question": "てがみ",
      "Narration": "tegami",
      "Answer": "letter"
    },
    {
      "Question": "くるま",
      "Narration": "kuruma",
      "Answer": "car"
    },
    {
      "Question": "じてんしゃ",
      "Narration": "jitensha",
      "Answer": "bicycle"
    },
    {
      "Question": "でんしゃ",
      "Narration": "densha",
      "Answer": "train"
    },
    {
      "Question": "えき",
      "Narration": "eki",
      "Answer": "station"
    },
    {
      "Question": "まち",
      "Narration": "machi",
      "Answer": "town"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ひと",
      "Narration": "hito",
      "Answer": "person"
    },
    {
      "Question": "いぬ",
      "Narration": "inu",
      "Answer": "dog"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ねこ",
      "Narration": "neko",
      "Answer": "cat"
    },
    {
      "Question": "とり",
      "Narration": "tori",
      "Answer": "bird"
    },
    {
      "Question": "さかな",
      "Narration": "sakana",
      "Answer": "fish"
    },
    {
      "Question": "かいもの",
      "Narration": "kaimono",
      "Answer": "shopping"
    },
    {
      "Question": "しごと",
      "Narration": "shigoto",
      "Answer": "work"
    },
    {
      "Question": "がっこう",
      "Narration": "gakkou",
      "Answer": "school"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ともだち",
      "Narration": "tomodachi",
      "Answer": "friend"
    },
    {
      "Question": "かぞく",
      "Narration": "kazoku",
      "Answer": "family"
    },
    {
      "Question": "おんがく",
      "Narration": "ongaku",
      "Answer": "music"
    },
    {
      "Question": "えいが",
      "Narration": "eiga",
      "Answer": "movie"
    },
    {
      "Question": "うた",
      "Narration": "uta",
      "Answer": "song"
    },
    {
      "Question": "おかし",
      "Narration": "okashi",
      "Answer": "sweets | snacks"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ぎゅうにゅう",
      "Narration": "gyuunyuu",
      "Answer": "milk"
    },
    {
      "Question": "みず",
      "Narration": "mizu",
      "Answer": "water"
    },
    {
      "Question": "あさ",
      "Narration": "asa",
      "Answer": "morning"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ひる",
      "Narration": "hiru",
      "Answer": "afternoon"
    },
    {
      "Question": "よる",
      "Narration": "yoru",
      "Answer": "night"
    },
    {
      "Question": "きょう",
      "Narration": "kyou",
      "Answer": "today"
    },
    {
      "Question": "あした",
      "Narration": "ashita",
      "Answer": "tomorrow"
    },
    {
      "Question": "きのう",
      "Narration": "kinou",
      "Answer": "yesterday"
    },
    {
      "Question": "うみ",
      "Narration": "umi",
      "Answer": "sea"
    },
    {
      "Question": "やま",
      "Narration": "yama",
      "Answer": "mountain"
    },
    {
      "Question": "かわ",
      "Narration": "kawa",
      "Answer": "river"
    },
    {
      "Question": "もり",
      "Narration": "mori",
      "Answer": "forest"
    },
    {
      "Question": "はな",
      "Narration": "hana",
      "Answer": "flower"
    },
    {
      "Question": "はる",
      "Narration": "haru",
      "Answer": "spring"
    },
    {
      "Question": "なつ",
      "Narration": "natsu",
      "Answer": "summer"
    },
    {
      "Question": "あき",
      "Narration": "aki",
      "Answer": "autumn"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ふゆ",
      "Narration": "fuyu",
      "Answer": "winter"
    },
    {
      "Question": "あお",
      "Narration": "ao",
      "Answer": "blue"
    },
    {
      "Question": "あか",
      "Narration": "aka",
      "Answer": "red"
    },
    {
      "Question": "しろ",
      "Narration": "shiro",
      "Answer": "white"
    },
    {
      "Question": "くろ",
      "Narration": "kuro",
      "Answer": "black"
    },
    {
      "Question": "きいろ",
      "Narration": "kiiro",
      "Answer": "yellow"
    },
    {
      "Question": "みどり",
      "Narration": "midori",
      "Answer": "green"
    },
    {
      "Question": "くつ",
      "Narration": "kutsu",
      "Answer": "shoes"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ぼうし",
      "Narration": "boushi",
      "Answer": "hat"
    },
    {
      "Question": "めがね",
      "Narration": "megane",
      "Answer": "glasses"
    },
    {
      "Question": "て",
      "Narration": "te",
      "Answer": "hand"
    },
    {
      "Question": "あし",
      "Narration": "ashi",
      "Answer": "foot/leg"
    },
    {
      "Question": "め",
      "Narration": "me",
      "Answer": "eye"
    },
    {
      "Question": "みみ",
      "Narration": "mimi",
      "Answer": "ear"
    },
    {
      "Question": "はな",
      "Narration": "hana",
      "Answer": "nose"
    },
    {
      "Question": "くち",
      "Narration": "kuchi",
      "Answer": "mouth"
    },
    {
      "Question": "かみ",
      "Narration": "kami",
      "Answer": "hair"
    },
    {
      "Question": "せ",
      "Narration": "se",
      "Answer": "height"
    },
    {
      "Question": "こえ",
      "Narration": "koe",
      "Answer": "voice"
    },
    {
      "Question": "こころ",
      "Narration": "kokoro",
      "Answer": "heart/mind"
    },
    {
      "Question": "あたま",
      "Narration": "atama",
      "Answer": "head"
    },
    {
      "Question": "どうぶつ",
      "Narration": "doubutsu",
      "Answer": "animal"
    },
    {
      "Question": "こうえん",
      "Narration": "kouen",
      "Answer": "park"
    },
    {
      "Question": "うち",
      "Narration": "uchi",
      "Answer": "home/house"
    },
    {
      "Question": "いえ",
      "Narration": "ie",
      "Answer": "house"
    },
    {
      "Question": "へや",
      "Narration": "heya",
      "Answer": "room"
    },
    {
      "Question": "まど",
      "Narration": "mado",
      "Answer": "window"
    },
    {
      "Question": "つくえ",
      "Narration": "tsukue",
      "Answer": "desk"
    },
    {
      "Question": "いす",
      "Narration": "isu",
      "Answer": "chair"
    },
    {
      "Question": "と",
      "Narration": "to",
      "Answer": "door"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ゆうびんきょく",
      "Narration": "yuubinkyoku",
      "Answer": "post office"
    },
    {
      "Question": "びょういん",
      "Narration": "byouin",
      "Answer": "hospital"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ほんや",
      "Narration": "honya",
      "Answer": "bookstore"
    },
    {
      "Question": "えいがかん",
      "Narration": "eigakan",
      "Answer": "movie theater"
    },
    {
      "Question": "こうばん",
      "Narration": "kouban",
      "Answer": "police box"
    },
    {
      "Question": "きっさてん",
      "Narration": "kissaten",
      "Answer": "cafe"
    },
    {
      "Question": "びじゅつかん",
      "Narration": "bijutsukan",
      "Answer": "art museum"
    },
    {
      "Question": "たべもの",
      "Narration": "tabemono",
      "Answer": "food"
    },
    {
      "Question": "のみもの",
      "Narration": "nomimono",
      "Answer": "drink"
    },
    {
      "Question": "さけ",
      "Narration": "sake",
      "Answer": "alcohol"
    },
    {
      "Question": "にく",
      "Narration": "niku",
      "Answer": "meat"
    },
    {
      "Question": "やさい",
      "Narration": "yasai",
      "Answer": "vegetable"
    },
    {
      "Question": "くだもの",
      "Narration": "kudamono",
      "Answer": "fruit"
    },
    {
      "Question": "りんご",
      "Narration": "ringo",
      "Answer": "apple"
    },
    {
      "Question": "みかん",
      "Narration": "mikan",
      "Answer": "mandarin orange"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ばなな",
      "Narration": "banana",
      "Answer": "banana"
    },
    {
      "Question": "いちご",
      "Narration": "ichigo",
      "Answer": "strawberry"
    },
    {
      "Question": "ぶどう",
      "Narration": "budou",
      "Answer": "grape"
    },
    {
      "Question": "すいか",
      "Narration": "suika",
      "Answer": "watermelon"
    },
    {
      "Question": "めろん",
      "Narration": "meron",
      "Answer": "melon"
    },
    {
      "Question": "もも",
      "Narration": "momo",
      "Answer": "peach"
    },
    {
      "Question": "みそ",
      "Narration": "miso",
      "Answer": "miso"
    },
    {
      "Question": "しお",
      "Narration": "shio",
      "Answer": "salt"
    },
    {
      "Question": "さとう",
      "Narration": "satou",
      "Answer": "sugar"
    },
    {
      "Question": "しょうゆ",
      "Narration": "shouyu",
      "Answer": "soy sauce"
    },
    {
      "Question": "こしょう",
      "Narration": "koshou",
      "Answer": "pepper"
    },
    {
      "Question": "さかな",
      "Narration": "sakana",
      "Answer": "fish"
    },
    {
      "Question": "にく",
      "Narration": "niku",
      "Answer": "meat"
    },
    {
      "Question": "たまご",
      "Narration": "tamago",
      "Answer": "egg"
    },
    {
      "Question": "にんじん",
      "Narration": "ninjin",
      "Answer": "carrot"
    },
    {
      "Question": "たまねぎ",
      "Narration": "tamanegi",
      "Answer": "onion"
    },
    {
      "Question": "じゃがいも",
      "Narration": "jagaimo",
      "Answer": "potato"
    },
    {
      "Question": "さとう",
      "Narration": "satou",
      "Answer": "sugar"
    },
    {
      "Question": "しお",
      "Narration": "shio",
      "Answer": "salt"
    },
    {
      "Question": "す",
      "Narration": "su",
      "Answer": "vinegar"
    },
    {
      "Question": "こめ",
      "Narration": "kome",
      "Answer": "rice"
    },
    {
      "Question": "みそ",
      "Narration": "miso",
      "Answer": "miso"
    }
  ]
}